Eddie Woods papers, circa 1957-2009 M1386
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
Eddie Woods papers
circa 1957- 2009
M1386
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
76.0 Linear feet (92 manuscript boxes, 2 half boxes, 4 flat boxes, 39 map folders, 1 roll; 161 audio cassettes, 11 VHS, 1 KCA64 videocassette, 1 8mm film reel, 1 HDV tape.)
This collection was compiled by Eddie Woods. The Eddie Woods papers document an understudied, indeed largely undefined, segment of the “new American poetry and prose” of the post-1945 period – namely, the expatriate and, to a certain extent, surrealist school that has numerous connections with the Beats but is essentially an independent, coherent body of work whose leading figures are represented in this collection by substantial numbers of manuscript materials, correspondence, scarce and rare books, photographs, and a variety of art prints, including numerous silk screensAn expatriate poet and publisher belonging to the essentially surrealist school of post-World War II writers in the late 1960s.
Woods, Eddie
Access to Collection
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Acquisition Information
This collection was purchased by Stanford University, Special Collections in July 2003. A small addenda was donated in 2007.
Arrangement
The Eddie Woods papers consist of personal and business correspondence, diaries, rare books and periodicals, manuscripts, ephemera, assorted printed matter, original artwork, photographs, and audiovisual materials, circa 1957-2009.
This collection is arranged into nine series: 1. Correspondence, 2. Ins and Outs, 3. Eddie Woods' Diaries, 4. Little Magazines, 5. Manuscripts by Eddie Woods, 6. Ephemera, Printed Matter, Photographs, and Artwork, 7. Jenny Brookes, 8. Unsolicited Manuscripts, 9. Audiovisual Materials.
Biographical and Historical Note
The Eddie Woods Archive documents an understudied, indeed largely undefined, segment of the “new American poetry and prose” of the post-1945 period – namely, the expatriate and, to a certain extent, surrealist school that has numerous connections with the Beats but is essentially an independent, coherent body of work. The leading figures of this school are represented in this collection by substantial numbers of manuscript materials, correspondence, scarce and rare books, photographs, and a variety of art prints, including numerous silk screens. The principal centers of this expatriate vein of post-WWII American cultural expression were Amsterdam, London, Morocco, Nepal, Bombay and other sites in India, Thailand, Bali, and to a lesser degree Paris. Eddie Woods (b. 1940, in New York) moved into this cultural circle in the early 1970s. Originally a journalist, he first made contact with it through his newspaper and radio work in Thailand, which was eventually followed by his becoming an editor for International Times (IT), a London-based monthly that was one of the counter-culture’s major voices in the 1960s and 1970s. Woods had begun writing poetry and fiction by this time, and after he moved to Amsterdam in the late 1970s, he founded Ins & Outs magazine, then subsequently the Ins & Outs Press and Bookstore, all of which flourished as publishers, publicists, and organizers of expatriate cultural productions from the late 70s and into the 80s (with the Press continuing into the early 90s). In October 2004 the Press emerged from a decade of ‘suspended animation’ with the release of Eddie Woods’ spoken-word CD Dangerous Precipice, followed a year later by his book Tsunami of Love: A Poems Cycle. The recorded version of Tsunami of Love appeared on compact disc in August 2007.
In his role as a cultural impresario and artistic entrepreneur, Eddie Woods, still an active poet and prose writer, is an important presence, both in American expatriate circles and among European avant-gardists, especially Dutch and Italian. Woods’ promotional activities made him, in short, a crucial center to the movement, and his archive documents his close connections with its leading figures, including Paul Bowles, Ira Cohen, Bob and Eileen Kaufman, Louise Landes-Levi, William Levy, and Jack Micheline.
The Archive also contains manuscripts and many photographs of the principal Beat writers, including William Burroughs, Gregory Corso, Allen Ginsberg, Herbert Huncke, and Harold Norse. It features, as well, significant documentation on numerous European avant-garde figures of the period, such as the British writer Tom Raworth, the Dutch photographer Peter Edel (including portraits of William Burroughs, Julian Beck, Allen Ginsberg, and Yevgeny Yevtushenko, along with annotated contact sheets), Piero Heliczer (Italian-born American poet, playwright and filmmaker), and Chris Sanders, long-time publisher of the International Times.
Aguila, Pancho, 1945-; Andre Codrescu; Brookes, Jenny; Burroughs, William S., 1914-1997; Clay, Mel; Cohen, Ira; Dorn, Edward; Ferlinghetti, Lawrence; Ginsberg, Allen, 1926-1997; Heliczer, Piero.; Hollander, Xaviera; Jim Haynes; Kerouac, Jan, 1952-; Levy, William; Micheline, Jack, 1929-; Miller, Henry, 1891-1980; Norse, Harold; Oisteanu, Valery; Plomp, Hans, 1944-; Raworth, Tom; Vinkenoog, Simon, 1928-; Williams, Heathcote; Williams, Tennessee, 1911-1983; Woods, Eddie; American literature--20th century; Poets, American--20th century.
- Series 1: Correspondence
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains personal as well as some business correspondence. Ins and Outs correspondence is described in Series 2. Ins and Outs. Additionally, Jenny Brookes' correspondence is described in Series 7. Jenny Brookes.
  - Abbott, Steve: Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abbott, Steve: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abbott, Steve: Correspondence (Incoming/Outgoing) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Abrams, Gerry: Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Aguila, Pancho: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Altoe, Remo Paul: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Altomare, Carlo: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Amsterdam Palette Union/Veldhoen, Aat and Christ: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Anderson, Floyd: Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Andre, Michael: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Antler: Correspondence and Poems (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Arietta, Ben: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Baarslag, Lee: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bangkok Post: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Barg, Barbara: Fresh Out of Nordland (Short Story) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Baroni, Vittore: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Baroni, Vittore: Mail Art (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Bassett, John: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bayley, Bruce: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Behre, Louis: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Behre, Louis: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Behre, Louis: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Behre, Louis: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Beltrametti, Franco: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Beltrametti, Franco: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Ben-Nun, Yaron: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Bennett, John: Correspondence and Books (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Bennett, Malcom: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Berge, Carol: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Beyer, Marion: Poetry (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Beyer, Marion: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Biederberg, Suzanne: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Black, Bob: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Black, Bob: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Blok, Diana: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Blok, Diana: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Blok, Diana: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Booms, Elisabeth: Ephemera (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Boutos, James: Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bowie, Angela: Poetry and Ephemera (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Bowles, Paul: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Bowles, Paul: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Bowles, Paul: Bouayad and the Money (Manuscript) and Ephemera (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Branca: Under Protest (Poem) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Breger, Udo: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Brewer, Wilmon: Poetry (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Bridges, Lee: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Brogger, Suzanne: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Brood, Herman: Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Brossard, Chandler: Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Brownstein, Michael: Essay (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Bruijn, Alexander de: Ephemera (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Bruner, Rick: Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Bryan, John: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Buck, Paul: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Burch, Charlton: Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Burke, Ronnie: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Burroughs, William: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Burroughs, William: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Burroughs, William: Ephemera (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Burroughs, William: International Times and Ephemera (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bystander, The: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Cafe Co Meyer: Ephemera and Correspondence (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Cafe Miller: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Capello, Rosemary: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Carpenter, Bruce (and Carola): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Chalmers, Gideon (Alan McGoldnick): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Chapman, Patrick: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Chapman, Patrick: Poetry and Ephemera (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Cheng, Ching Ho: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Cherkovski, Neeli: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Christie, Stuart: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Clay, Mel: Calcutta and a Woman Reading Borges (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Clay, Mel: Calcutta and a Woman Reading Borges (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Clay, Mel: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Clay, Mel: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Clay, Mel: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Clay, Mel: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Clay, Mel: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Clay, Mel: Henry Miller in Brooklyn (Play) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Clay, Mel: Personality Kult (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Clay, Mel: Personality Kult (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Clay, Mel: Personality Kult (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Clay, Mel: Poetry and Ephemera (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Clay, Mel: Poetry, Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Clay, Mel: Sexchange: A Dramatized Sensation (Play) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Clay, Mel: Correspondence, 1981-1989 (Incoming/Outgoing) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Clay, Mel: Correspondence,1980-1981 (Incoming/Outgoing) (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Clay, Mel: Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Incoming/Outgoing) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Clay, Mel: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Clements, Alan: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Codrescu, Andrei: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Codrescu, Andrei: Exquisite Corpse (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Cohen, Elaine: Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Cohen, Ira: Books (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Cohen, Ira: Correspondence, 1980s (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Cohen, Ira: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cohen, Ira: Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Cohen, Ira: Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Cohen, Ira: Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Cohen, Ira: Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Cohen, Ira: Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Cohen, Ira: Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Cohen, Ira: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Cohen, Ira: Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Cohen, Ira: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Cohen, Ira: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Cohen, Ira: Correspondence (Incoming/Outgoing) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Cohen, Ira: The Occult and the Supernatural: The World of the Unexplained (Book) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Cohen, Ira: Printed Matter (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Cohen, Ira: Printed Matter (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Cohen, Sue: End Point (Short Story) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Colauto, Bobby: Correspondence and Poetry (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Coleman, Wanda: Correspondence and Poetry (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Cooper, Dennis: Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Corso, Gregory: Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Crawford, Steve: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Da. Lottie: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Dalchinsky, Steve: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Dallman, Jeanne: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Danielian, Ruth: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Darlington, Andrew: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Davidson, Steef: Correspondence and Poetry (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Davis, Glen: Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - DeGroot, Henk: Correspondence and Legal Documents (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - DeGroot, Henk: Correspondence and Legal Documents (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - DeGroot, Henk: Correspondence and Legal Documents (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - DeGroot, Henk: Correspondence and Receipts (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - DeGroot, Henk: Correspondence and Receipts (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - DeGroot, Henk: Correspondence and Receipts (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - DeGroot, Henk: Correspondence and Receipts (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - DeGroot, Henk: Correspondence and Receipts (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - DeGroot, Henk: Correspondence and Receipts (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - DeGroot, Henk: Lawsuit Dossier (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - DeGroot, Henk: Lawsuit Dossier (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - DeGroot, Henk: Correspondence and Legal Documents (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - DeGroot, Henk: Correspondence and Legal Documents (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - DeGroot, Henk: Correspondence and Legal Documents (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - de Jong, Daan: Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Devit, Mario J. ("Marty"): Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Diana, Juanita: Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - DiLauro, Stephen: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Doran, Barbara and Frank Seiple: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Dorn, Edward: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Dowden, Kaviraj George: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Dreyer, Ronnie: Astrological Materials (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Dreyer, Ronnie: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Dreyer, Ronnie: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Dreyer, Ronnie: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Dwyer, Ed: Correspondence (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Earl, Rob: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Edel, Peter: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Einhorn, Nikolaus: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Ellwood, Russell: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Enting, Pat: Correspondence and Poetry (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Essary, Loris: Correspondence and An Incidence of Camelopards (Play) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Estes, Patricia (nee Patti-Jo Keough): Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Estes, Patricia (nee Patti-Jo Keough): Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Estes, Patricia (nee Patti-Jo Keough): Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Estes, Patricia (nee Patti-Jo Keough): Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Estes, Patricia (nee Patti-Jo Keough): Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Estes, Patricia (nee Patti-Jo Keough): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Estes, Patricia (nee Patti-Jo Keough): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Estes, Patricia (nee Patti-Jo Keough): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Estes, Patricia (nee Patti-Jo Keough): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Estes, Patricia (nee Patti-Jo Keough): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Falk, Jane: Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Fargas, Jaume: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Ferlinghetti, Lawrence: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Fertig, Gary: Correspondence and Calendarus Propheticus (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Firsoff, George: Correspondence, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - First International Cannabis Conference: Ephemera and Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - First International Canabis Conference: Ephemera (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Fischer, Raaja: Speeches for the Age of Sharing (Essay) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Flux: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Ford, Charles Henri: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Ford, Roderick (Rod): Correspondence and Poetry (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Ford, Roderick (Rod): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Ford, Terry: Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Fox, Hugh (and Connie Fox): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Fox, Walter Q. (Pseudonym, Vladimir Lysenko): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Frestonia: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Friar Kimon: Correspondence and Poetry (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Friedman, Paul: Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Froggett, Nicholas: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Fry, Sandra: Correspondence and Poetry (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Gach, Gary: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Galea, Vic and Micahel Gartner: Correspondence (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Ganesh Baba: Ephemera and Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Garrett, William: Ephemera and Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Gatewood, Charles: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Gentle Ghost: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Ginsberg, Allen: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Glubin, Cherly: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Goenka, S.N.: Correspondence and Interview (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Goodman, Jim: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Goss, Ian and Sue: Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Green, Surya (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Green, Theo: Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Grillo, Paul: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Gysin, Brion: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Hagedorn, Jessica: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Hamel, Niels: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Hamilton, Fritz: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Handley, Max: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Hannum, John: Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Harlee, John T.: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Harvey, Jane: Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Harvey, Jane: Correspondence (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Harvey, Jane: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Harvey, Jane: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Hayet: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Haynes, Jesper: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Haynes, Jim: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Heliczer, Piero: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Heliczer, Piero: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Helms, Michael: Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Henderson, David: Correspondence (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Henn, Max: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Hertz, Uri: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Hewison, Rowan: Short Story Manuscripts (3) (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Hiddema, Bert: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Hirschman, Jack: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Hollander, Xavier: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Hollander, Xavier: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Hollander, Xavier: Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Hollander, Xavier: Correspondence, The Happy Hooker with personal inscription to Eddie Woods, and Ephemera (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Hollander, Xavier: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Hollis, Carl: Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Hoogstraten, Harry: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Hoogstraten, Harry: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Hoopen, Peter ten: The True Life of Jesus of Nazareth (Manuscript) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Horovitz, Michael: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Huges, Bart: Ephemera (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Huncke, Herbert: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Hutchings, Nina: Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Israel, Steve Ben: Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Jackson, Julie Kay: Kali: A Force of Liberation (Essay) (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Jackson, Ted: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Joans, Ted: Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Jones, Jay Jeffrey: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Jonge, Wim de: Poems (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Kagie, Eddie: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Kaliszewski, Ian: Correspondence, Some Queer Things (Manuscript), and Illustrated Manuscript of Veblen's Theory of Leisure Class (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Karol, Pamala (pseudonym: La Loca): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Kathmandu: Chapbooks (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Kathmandu: Chapbooks, Ephemera, and Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Katmor, Jacques and Ann Katmor: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Katmor, Jacques and Ann Katmor: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Kaufman, Eileen (and Bob Kaufman): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Kaufman, Eileen (and Bob Kaufman): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Kaufman, Eileen (and Bob Kaufman): Who Wouldn't Walk With Tigers (Manuscript) (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Kaviaar, Joke: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Kennedy, Anne: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Kerouac, Jan: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Klinger, Barry: Correspondence and Business Cards (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Knight, Arthur and Kit: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Koertge, Ron: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Koller, James: Poems (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Koran, Dennis: Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Kostelanetz, Richard: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Kupferberg, Tuli: Correspondence and Cartoons (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Kush (Kushner, Steven): Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - L'Amour, Fifi: Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Lambiek: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Landgarten, Ira: Correspondence and Photographs (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Laufi: Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Leighton, Andy and Lukas, David Scott: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Lemoine, Elisabeth: Ephemera and Correspondence [original owner of Eddie Woods' dog Snuffie] (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Leyland, Winston: Correspondence and Poem (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Levy, Louise Landes: Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Levi, Louise Landes: Poems, Correspondence, and Ephemera (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Levi, Louise Landes: Correspondence, Poems, and Ephemera (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Levy, Louise Landes: Correspondence, Poems, and Ephemera (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Levy, William: Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 2)